不
No!
走
Hey! Go!
那是谁
The hell was that?
我不知道
I don't know.
- 我们得帮帮他 - 不 你们快跑
- We have to get him help. -No. You need to run.
我叫丹尼 我正在追杀手和会的人
My name is Danny. I'm hunting members of the Hand.
我想你就是我们要找的人
I think you're the man we're looking for.
铁拳
Iron Fist.
回去吧
Go home.
你知道我是谁
You know who I am?
你的战斗 不在这里
The war you're fighting... it's not here.
而在纽约
It's in New York City.
别 嘿
No... No! Hey!
嘿
Hey.
关门了
Closing time.
回家吧
Go home.
拜托 晚上才刚刚开始好吧
Come on, the night's just getting started.
晚上
Night?
该死
Ah, shit!
不
No!
先生 先生
Excuse me! Excuse me, sir!
我很抱歉
No, um, I'm so sorry.
- 这是我的车 - 不再是了
- This is my car. - Not anymore.
今早9点开始这就是市政财产了 你停在了装卸专用区域
At nine a.M., it became city property. Loading zone only.
- 求你了 我可以挪走 - 已经挂上拖车了
- Please. I can move it. - Not once it's hitched.
但你可以在下午六点前
But you can come to the impound
到49号大街的扣押区认领取回你的车
on 49th to reclaim it any time before six p.M.
洛伊德 你在干什么
Lloyd, what the hell are you doing?
什么
What?
有问题吗
We got a problem?
我昨天接到一个电话
I got a call yesterday.
又一个制片人想拍你的故事
A second producer who wants to tell your story.
没门
Hard pass.
纽约喜欢赢家 不管你怎么想
New York loves a winner, and like it or not,
你打败一个超级大反派
you stood up to a really awful person and won.
你知道要达到你现在这种宣传热度 政论家们得开价多高吗
You know how much publicists charge for that kind of attention?
要花多少钱才能让这个热度下去
How much to make it stop?
我只是说 你可以考虑一下
I'm just saying, you might wanna consider it.
在你再次工作前 这可以帮你糊口
It could help keep your bills paid until you start working again.
- 我还饿不死 - 暂时而已
- My bills aren't a problem. - Not yet.
你好歹有开始接业务电话吧
Have you at least started answering the phone?
只有你才能把这种大好事看做坏事
Only you could turn that big personal victory into a defeat.
- 你知道你问题在哪吗 -
- You know what your problem is? - Sentences that start like that.
你还不能接受你现在的身份
You're not comfortable with what you've become.
杰西卡 你现在是一个
Jessica, you are now a
- 十足的超级英 - 别说那个词
- full-blown super-- -Do not say the H-word.
杰西卡 我已经很头痛了
Jess, I-- -I've got enough of a headache as it is.
我只是说 你可以回家 睡一觉
I'm just saying, you might wanna consider going home,
然后重返现实社会
getting some sleep, rejoining society.
我不是在和你说话嘛
I'm talking to you.
我很感激这一点
And I appreciate that.
- 这里面是有威士忌吗 - 哦对 这杯是我的
- Is there whiskey in this? -Oh, yeah, that's mine.
看来你把上头各项关系都疏通好了
Looks like all of your paper-pushing worked.
放这个超级明星走吧 让他离开这里
Uncuff the superstar. Get him out of my sight.
我的错
My bad.
这是你的
These belong to you.
卢卡斯先生 还是凯奇先生
Mr. Lucas? Mr. Cage?
- 你喜欢哪个 我忘了 - 凯奇
- Which do you prefer? I forget. - Cage.
- 我认识你吗 - 富兰克林 尼尔森
- Do I know you? -Franklin Nelson.
你的案子是我处理的 我们通过很多次电话
I ran point on your case. We spoke on the phone... A lot.
你话很多
You spoke a lot.
只有在工作的时候
As long as it worked.
- 谢谢 - 谢你朋友鲍比 菲什吧
- I appreciate it. - Appreciate your friend Bobby Fish.
我们可是翻阅了好多材料
We all did some impressive book-cracking.
再说 你毫发无伤
Plus, you made it through a
就逃出了监狱
prison stint without throwing a single punch.
我相信这很难吧 对于像你这样
I'm sure that was hard for a person with your...
- 我知道 - 名声的人
- I know. -...reputation.
- 克莱尔来了吗 - 这里只有律师能进
- Is, uh... Claire coming? -It's lawyers only in here.
请见谅 我还得去赶公交
Well, if you'll excuse me, I have a bus to catch.
当然 噢 最后一件事
Of course. Uh, just one last thing.
霍加斯 赵 本诺维茨律所为您服务
The law firm of Hogarth, Chao & Benowitz is at your disposal.
如果你需要帮忙重新开始
In case you need help starting over.
我不打算重新开始 尼尔森先生
I'm not starting over, Mr. Nelson.
我会向前看的
I'm moving forward.
人们叫我福基
People call me Foggy.
你居然愿意让人这么叫你
And you let them?
根据在案记录 你曾说50号和10号大街的新
You're on record as saying that the new subway station
地铁站将会是 引用你的原话 有益公众的
at 50th and 10th would be, quote, "Good for the community."
完全是引用原话 有益公众的
Would be quote-- quote, unquote, "Good for the community."
伯克维兹先生 以你专业
Mr. Berkowitz, in your professional-- -
你在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
干嘛 我要打爆你的狗头
'Sup, man? I'll bust your goddamn head!
- 是吗 我们走 - 发生了什么
- Oh, yeah? Let's go, then. - What's up?
- 你想试试吗 - 快点 我们走
- You wanna try something? - Come at me. Let's go!
纽约警察局 散开 够了
NYPD! Break it up! That's enough.
- 你 到人行道上去 - 好的警官
- You, up on the sidewalk. - Yes, sir, officer.
伯克维兹先生
Mr. Berkowitz...
从你专业观点来看 这个地铁站对亚伦 詹姆斯有益了吗
In your professional opinion, was it good for Aaron James?
我们深切同情这个家庭的不幸遭遇
Our sympathies go out to the family.
整件事 非常不幸
The whole thing... It's very unfortunate.
你那时候知道这些在你
Were you aware the products used
新地铁站使用的产品对孩子有害吗
in your new station were hazardous to children?
- 反对 - 我会换个说法
- Objection! -I'll rephrase.
你使用的这种橡胶有哪些优点
What was attractive about Endexoprene?
强韧 耐久
It's strong. It's durable.
- 以及价格便宜一半 - 我是做生意的
- And half the price? - Well, I do run a business.
为了节约钱就把人们置于危险之中 值得吗
Is it worth endangering people in the interest of saving money?
所有材料都是测试过的
All materials are tested.
在发现该产品有危害的报告公之于众以后
The moment those findings were made public,
我们公司立刻更换了剩下所有地铁站内使用的橡胶粉砂浆
our company replaced that mortar in all remaining stations.
公之于众
"Made public."
这是什么意思
What do you mean?
你是指那份9月29号公布的报告吗
Are you referring to a report released on September 29th?
法官大人 他正在要求
Your Honor, he's asking my
我的委托人回答不合理的具体细节
client to respond with unreasonable specificity.
伯克维兹先生 如果我没有记错
Mr. Berkowitz, if memory serves me right,
三个月之前 你的办公室曾在6月3号
your office received an urgent delivery
收到过一份来自安全委员会的紧急文件
from the Safety Commission on June 3rd. Three months earlier.
我很好奇 这是否与本案中有质量问题的橡胶有关呢
I'm curious, did that have anything to do with Endexoprene?
我对此毫不知情
I don't know anything about that.
法官大人 除非默多克先生
Your Honor, unless Mr. Murdock
可以证明我的委托人确实
can prove my client actually
收到了这些他口中所谓的文件 否则
received these hypothetical documents, then--
这与他收没收到那份文件无关
It's not about whether he received them.
而是在于他是否刻意忽略了它
It's whether he willfully ignored them.
法官大人 我要求将这份紧急文件的
Your Honor, I ask that this
发送记录作为证据呈上
record of delivery be admitted into evidence.
- 我是说 我每天收到很多类似的文件 - 你觉得哪种情况更糟
- I mean, I get a lot of those. - What would you say is worse?
为削减成本而忽视重要的相关数据
Ignoring data in the interest of cutting costs?
还是出于过失而没有像法庭提供能够证明你
Or neglecting to supply the court with records that might prove
你有意陷他人与危险之中的记录
you purposely put people in danger?
- 包括 - 法官大人
- Including - Your Honor
包括这位年轻人
Including this young man,
亚伦 詹姆斯 他可能永远都没法走路了
Aaron James, who might never walk again.
- 法官大人 我们申请休庭 - 不需要 我讲完了
- Your Honor, we would like a recess. - No need. I'm done.
我觉得他也要玩完了
I think he is, too.
一千一百万美金的赔偿款
$11 million!
谢谢你 默多克先生
Thank you, Mr. Murdock.
- 这是我的荣幸 - 谢谢
- Oh, my pleasure. -Thank you.
我真为你感到高兴
I'm so happy for you.
天哪
God.
嗨
Hey.
- 你还好吗 - 是的
- You okay? - Yeah.
介意我告诉你一些事情吗
Mind if I tell you something?
讲吧
Sure.
这笔钱对你父母很有帮助
That money is really gonna help your parents.
但是对你来说 从现在起
But for you, from here on out...
一切只会变得更难 亚伦
it's only gonna get harder, Aaron.
你知道你艰难的人生马拉松才刚刚开始
You realize you're only at mile one of the marathon...
对吧
right?
所有人都会告诉你应该要怎么想
Everybody's gonna tell you how to feel.
医生会叫你保持乐观
Doctors are gonna tell you to stay positive.
你的家人会告诉你不要为自己感到悲哀
Your family's gonna tell you not to feel sorry for yourself.
你的治疗师会告诉你不要生气
Your therapist is gonna tell you not to be angry--
我已经很生气了
I'm already angry.
对谁生气
At who?
所有人
Everyone.
我只想回到从前的生活
I just want my life back.
这是不可能的
They can't give you that.
或许你能重新走路
Maybe you'll walk again.
希望你可以做到
I hope so.
但是也许你做不到
But maybe you won't.
但在这个愈发艰难的过程中 学会面对这一切
But your ability to get through it... as this gets harder...
比强颜欢笑
that is a hundred times more
假装一切都好
powerful than slapping a smile on your face
要重要一百倍
and pretending like everything's just fine.
你能明白吗
Do you understand?
嘿 听着
Hey, listen...
没有人可以让你回到以前的生活 亚伦
no one can give you your life back, Aaron.
你必须 你只能靠自己
You have... You gotta take it back.
我们走吧
Let's go.
恭喜你 默多克先生
Congratulations, Mr. Murdock.
哦 谢谢你 佩奇小姐
Oh. Thank you, Ms. Page.
没关系的 你可以为自己感到
It's okay. You can be proud of yourself.
一点点骄傲 我不会告诉其他人的
A little. I won't tell anyone.
你 是来采访我的吗
You, uh, here for a statement?
是的
Uh, yeah.
嘿 你想不想去 边吃边做采访
Hey, you maybe wanna go... do that over a bite or...
哦 额 当然了
Oh, uh... Sure, yeah.
- 额 可以给我5分钟吗 - 好的
- Um... can you give me five minutes? - Mm-hmm.
- 默多克先生 - 默多克先生
- Mr. Murdock... - Mr. Murdock, sir...
怎么了
Yes...
你抛弃了他们
You abandoned them.
拜你所赐 手和会赢了
Because of you, the Hand has won.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
在他们把你培养起来之后
After they raised you...
他们给了你一切 你
after they gave you everything you are...
你却任他们死去
you let them die.
不
No.
不是的
No!
- 丹尼 醒醒 - 不
- Danny. Wake up. -No!
不
No!
丹尼
Danny.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
只是 只是因为有点颠簸
It's just the... It's just the turbulence.
我觉得我永远都没法习惯飞机的颠簸了
I don't think I'll ever get used to it.
- 丹尼 - 我
- Danny... - I'm...
我要去找机长
I'm gonna go check with the pilot.
丹尼
Danny.
你要和我聊聊你的想法吗
Are you gonna talk to me about whatever's on your mind?
听着 这
Look, it was...
我什么都没想
It was nothing.
你刚才又在尖叫了
You were screaming. Again.
我没事
I'm fine.
我觉得我们对于 没事 的理解不太一样
I think we have different understandings of the word "Fine."
我们已经追踪手和会好几个月了
We've been chasing the Hand for months.
我们终于找到了一个或许可以帮助我们的人了
We finally get a lead on a guy who can supposedly help us...
可等我们赶到那里 却只能眼睁睁看着他死了
and we get there just in time to watch him die.
这不是你的错
It is not your fault.
那个女人在我手下逃走了
I let that woman escape.
你又不是故意让她逃走的
You didn't let anyone do anything.
不管她是谁 我从没见过这么快的移动速度
Whoever she was, she moved faster than anyone I've ever seen.
是的
Yeah.
她的进攻速度也很快
She hit like it, too.
一定是手合会的人 是吧
It had to be the Hand, right?
我不确定
I don't know.
手合会里还有许多我不知道的秘密勾当
There are a lot of things that the Hand kept from me.
这些勾当可没有那么容易对付
They're not the kind of problem that's gonna go away easily,
不过我们会弄明白的
but we can figure this out.
一起弄明白
Together.
这帮人想在纽约干什么
What do they want in New York?
请把衣服都脱了 首饰也请取下
You'll need to disrobe. Jewelry and all.
抱歉让你久等了
Sorry to keep you waiting.
上一轮测试的
The results of the last
结果已经和你说明白了 对吗
round of tests were explained to you, yes?
测试结果很明确
They're rather conclusive, I'm afraid.
我的意思是
And by that, of course, what I mean to say is...
我要死了
I'm dying.
我的红细胞数量骤减
My red blood cell count has dropped precipitously
每个重要的器官也将近衰竭
and almost every one of my major organs is close to collapse.
情况还是这样吗
Is that still the case?
你能怎么治疗呢
What can you do to treat it?
老实说 这么急转直下的情况已回天乏术
To be honest, this kind of free fall is off the charts.
说这个有什么用
That's not helpful.
我问你的是还能做点什么
Or even what I asked.
好吧 不幸的是 即便如您一般拥有十分强大的资源
Well, unfortunately, even for someone with your resources...
我们也做不了什么了
there's not much we can do.
呃
Um...
我还剩多少时间
how much time do I have left?
几个月 或者几个星期
Could be months. Could be weeks.
做个检查能给出更准确的答案
I think this should give us more definitive answers.
这边请
Please.
开始吧
Let's begin.
天呐 我擦
Jesus. Shit.
琼斯小姐吗
Ms. Jones?
我是米歇尔 雷蒙德
My name is Michelle Raymond.
这是我的女儿 请帮帮我们
This is my daughter, Lexi. We need your help.
我无能为力
I can't.
抱歉 我们这么冒昧地来到你这
I'm sorry. We weren't sure if we were in the right place.
我现在帮不了你们 以后也不行
Not today. Probably not tomorrow, either.
- 算了吧 妈妈 - 我知道你的事迹
- Come on, Mom. - I read about what you did.
她根本不在乎
She doesn't give a shit.
- 我的丈夫不见了 - 她反正只是个行走的废柴
- My husband is missing. - She's a walking shit show anyway.
- 你说什么 - 莱克茜 别这样
- Excuse me? - Lexi, please.
我们的情况不太好 他已经一周没有消息了
We are not doing great. He has been gone a full week.
- 你报警了吗 - 没有
- Did you call the cops? - No.
- 为什么不呢 警察帮你可不收费 - 这不是钱的问题
- Why not? They're free. - Money is not an issue.
事情有蹊跷 我敢肯定 约翰一直很有规律
Something is wrong and I know it. John's like clockwork.
他是建筑师 每天早上8点去上班
He's an architect. He goes to work every morning at eight.
傍晚6:30回家
He comes back home every night at 6:30.
- 但是最近他 - 变得不一样 行踪隐秘
- But lately, he's... -He's been different? Secretive?
- 然后还有点神经质吗 - 一点都不像他
- Maybe even a little nervous? - And it's not like him.
那是因为他背着你偷情 好吗
Because he's cheating on you, okay?
你别不好意思 这种事太多了
Nothing to be ashamed about. It happens all the time.
- 你不了解他 - 我没必要了解他
- You don't know him like I do. - I don't need to.
是你来找我 我也给了你我的专业看法
But you came to me and I'm giving you my professional opinion.
你该去找离婚律师
You need a divorce lawyer.
谢谢您的帮助 琼斯小姐
Thank you for your time, Ms. Jones.
我真是谢谢你了
Yeah, thanks so much.
等会
Hey.
不管他现在怎样 我希望你们能找到他
Whatever he's doing... I hope you find him.
你打错了
Wrong number.
杰西卡 琼斯
Jessica Jones,
你别自招麻烦 不要去找约翰 雷蒙德
do yourself a favor and don't look for John Raymond.
喂
Hello?
你好 陌生人
Hey, stranger.
一起喝杯咖啡怎么样
Should we get that coffee?
等你出现可真是没准头啊
Waiting on you was a heck of a gamble.
据我所知 你可不擅长这个
For all I knew, you could've sucked at this.
是吗
Yeah?
- 嗯 - 希望你没白等
- Mm-hmm. - Well, I hope I was worth it.
你很有潜力
You got potential.
- 潜力 是吗 - 嗯哼
- "Potential"? Yeah? -Mm-hmm.
嗯
Mm-hmm
在监狱里有段很艰难的日子
There were some really rough days inside.
是你写的信 让我撑了过来
But your letters... they got me through it.
我都不记得我上回手写信是什么时候了
I can't remember the last time I handwrote a letter.
- 有次里面有一首诗 - 天呐
- There was that poem that one time. - Oh, God.
- 别这样 那首诗很不错 - 谢谢你
- No, it was a good one. - Thank you.
- 我是说 像是尼奇 吉奥瓦尼的 - 嘘
- I mean, it was also Nikki Giovanni. -Shh!
尼奇·吉奥瓦尼:上世纪60、70年代著名非裔美国诗人
尼奇·吉奥瓦尼 上世纪60、70年代著名非裔美国诗人
- 不错的 - 我们可没有都跟你似的那么多陈词滥调
- Yeah. - We all can't be your corny ass.
陈词滥调也比抄袭别人的好多了
Hey, I'd rather be corny than to plagiarize.
痛
Ow!
我在这些信里注意到一些
There was something else I noticed about your letters...
你没说的事情
What you didn't say.
- 卢克 - 听着 我知道这套路
- Luke... - Look, I know the drill.
我被关进去了 你觉得有些事你不能告诉我
Man goes inside, you think there are things you can't tell him.
但是不管在哈林区发生了什么 我要弄清楚
But whatever's going on in Harlem... I'm gonna find out.
听着 我们就不能好好享受这点时光吗
Look, can't we just enjoy this part a little longer?
我得知道
I need to know.
哈林区经历了一些变化
Harlem's gone through changes.
这是无法避免的
It was bound to happen.
玛利亚在干嘛
What's Mariah doing?
就跟你走之前一样
The same shit she was doing when you left.
好吧 现在你要担心的只剩下你自己了
Look, right now, the only thing you need to worry about is you.
如果你说的是找工作
Look, if you're talking about getting a job,
我可全心全意想找呢
I have every intention of doing just that.
做什么
Doing what?
你成了哈林区的英雄 哪还能有什么自己的生活
How does being Harlem's hero allow you to live an actual life?
我会有办法的
I'll find a way.
现在
Right now, just...
我只想帮助人们
I just wanna help people.
我也想这么做
I wanna do that, too.
你可以说我自私 但是我更希望你照顾好自己
But call me selfish... I wanna see you take care of yourself.
谁啊
Hello?
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hey. - Hey.
- 祝你好运 - 谢谢
- Good look. - Thanks.
抱歉打搅了 但是很高兴看到你已经安顿好了
Sorry to interrupt. But I'm glad to see you're settling in.
嘿 米丝蒂 很高兴见到你
Hey, Misty. It's good to see you.
也很高兴见到你 卢克
Good to see you, too, Luke.
你怎么找到我的
How did you know where to find me?
开玩笑 你可是哈林区的英雄
Are you kidding? You're the hero of Harlem.
想出去走走吗
Wanna come for a walk?
- 其实我 - 不会占用你太长时间 我保证
- Actually, I was, uh - It won't take long, I promise.
二号桌的菜好了
Number two in the window.
上周发生的事挺有趣
Great story last week.
关于那个学校董事会的丑闻
The, uh... thing with the school board scandal.
谢谢 埃里森现在基本上让我自主工作
Thank you. Yeah, Ellison's pretty much given me free reign.
感觉像是我注定要去
It feels like what I'm meant to be doing or...
我知道这听起来说不通
I don't know if that makes any sense.
是啊 当然
Yeah. Of course.
看起来你在做你一直想做的事
It looks like you're doing what you always wanted to.
是啊 从尼尔森和默多克律所到现在和
Yeah, it's been a transition from the Nelson and Murdock days,
大律所的合伙 确实经历了一个过渡期
from the partnership but, uh...
嗯 打无偿法律援助的案子我还是挺高兴的
No, the pro bono work does make me happy.
- 真棒 真是太 - 要咖啡吗
- That's great. That's really-- - Coffee?
- 好 谢谢 - 谢谢
- Yes, thank you. - Thanks.
糖在左边 奶在右边
Sugar's on the left. Cream's here on the right.
- 奶油在右边 谢谢 - 不客气
- Cream on the right. Thank you. - Yes. You're welcome.
- 对不起 - 是啊
- Sorry, it got... - Yeah.
你会希望你一直就自己保守着你的秘密吗
Do you wish you'd kept your secret to yourself?
不
No.
我需要你知道
I needed you to know.
我不确定自己在期待什么
I don't know what I expected,
但是我 我确定我不能再骗你了
but I... I know I couldn't lie to you anymore.
谢谢 我很感激你这么说
Thanks. I appreciate that.
你想念它吗
Do you miss it?
战衣 面具
The suit? The mask?
不
No.
就好像我人生中的这一章已经谢幕了
It feels like a chapter of my life that's closed.
我不后悔 你知道的 我只是
Now, I don't regret it. You know, I just...
- 我后悔因此赶跑了很多人 - 不
- I regret that it drove some people away. - No, it...
听着 你的秘密没有把我赶跑 我只是
Look, it didn't drive me away. I just...
我觉得我们
You know, I felt like we
应该先解决好自己的问题
should figure ourselves out first or something.
我一直在尝试
I'm trying.
嗯
Hmm.
尽管我感觉所有的这些事
You know, as complicated
都是那么的复杂 我只是
as I feel about all this stuff, I just...
我觉得你应该知道
I feel like you should know.
纽约警局现在干实事了
The NYPD is prevailing.
我每天都报道他们的事儿 犯罪率也确实下降了
I report on it every day, and crime rate's down.
我确实认为
I really think that
夜魔侠让这个城市更安全了
Daredevil may have made the city a safer place.
也许有他的功劳
He might have.
但是现在 这个城市没有了他更好
But right now, the city's better off without him.
嗯
Hmm.
有马克 默多克在的纽约城更好
Well, it's better off with Matt Murdock.
说到这事 默多克先生
Speaking of which, Mr. Murdock...
我想问问你对今天
I would like to take your
亚伦 詹姆斯一案判决的看法
statement on today's miraculous Aaron James verdict.
放马过来吧
Hit me.
嘿
Hey.
- 不行 - 干嘛
- No. - What?
你别再那么干了
We are not doing that thing
随随便便到这来 就跟去你家一样
where you come in here like you live here.
- 是你给我的钥匙 - 是你没经过我同意
- You gave me a key. - You took the spare key
就给家里换锁的时候自己拿的备用钥匙
when you changed the locks without my permission.
门坏了 我是在帮你的忙
Door was broken, and I was doing you a favor.
- 你想干嘛 马尔科姆 - 就来喝个汽水
- What do you want, Malcolm? - Just came for soda.
- 哦 我们现在在干嘛 - 我们现在啥事儿没干
- Ooh! So what are we doing? - We are doing nothing.
你接了个案子 我看得出来
You took a case. I can tell.
- 你脸上有那种兴奋 - 我没接什么案子
- You've got that glow about you. - I did not take a case...
- 目前还没有 - 那是谁
- yet. - Who is that?
- 别从我肩膀后面看 - 好吧
- Don't read over my shoulder. - Okay.
是个建筑师 对吗
It's an architect, huh?
- 又是一个偷情的 - 也许
- Another cheater? - Maybe.
他妻子来我这 迫切地想找到他
His wife showed up desperate to find him.
她说了一大堆我之前就听过的事
She said a bunch of stuff I've heard before.
你知道 意思就是 他是个正人君子 他很反常
You know, "He's squeaky clean. This is unlike him."
但是后来我接了通电话
But then I got a call.
有人用声音干扰器告诉我不要接这个案子
Someone used a voice scrambler and told me not to take the case.
我猜你就喜欢这种 是不是
Bet you loved that, didn't you?
毕业于麻省理工学院
Graduated MIT.
在迪拜设计了两座摩天楼 在曼哈顿也设计了四座楼
Designed two skyscrapers in Dubai and four in Manhattan.
他确实是个正人君子 你认为她妻子说得没错
He is squeaky clean. You think she's right?
也许 又或者他厌倦了当个好人
Maybe. Maybe he's tired of being the good guy.
也许他酗酒 也许他跟哪个实习生搞上了
Maybe he's on a bender. Maybe he's knee-deep in some intern.
- 恶心 - 非常恶心
- Gross. - Very.
所以 你有什么线索
So, what are your leads?
我根本没在找线索
I'm not looking for leads,
马尔科姆 因为我还没接这个案子
Malcolm, because I haven't take the case.
是啊 你试着追踪他的电话了吗
Yeah, right. Have you tried tracking the call yet?
行不通 电话号码能重新路由
It doesn't work that way. You can reroute phone numbers.
我是说 也许他没在号码上做手脚
I mean, maybe he didn't, though.
也许他只是个想要让你别找他的人
Maybe he's just a regular guy trying to throw you off the scent.
- 也许 - 也许他是个业余的
- Maybe - Maybe he's an amateur.
你好 我刚刚接到一个被屏蔽号码的电话
Hi. I just got a call from a blocked number.
我想知道你是否能告诉是从哪里打来的
I was wondering if you can tell me where it was coming from.
你能帮帮我嘛
Is there anything that you can do?
你知道的 我觉得电话应该是我祖父打来的 他年纪非常大了
You know, I think it's my grandfather and he's senile
他可能在尝试找到我
and he might be trying to get a hold of me.
事实上 我这里有一个失踪人员的报告
Actually, I have a missing person's report.
我这里正有一个号码
I have the number right in front of me.
如果你需要我可以读给你
I can read it to you if you want.
真的吗 太感谢你了
Really? Thank you so much.
这年头还有谁会用公用电话啊
Who the hell uses pay phones anymore?
- 在哪里 - 第11街和第49街交叉路口
- Where? - 11th and 49th.
好吧 我知道这个地方
Ugh, I know this place.
如果你要找的那个人在那个街区做些见不得人的事 那他就在那儿
If your guy's doing shady shit on that block, that's where he is.
我曾经磕过海洛因
I used to do heroin.
我懂的不多
I don't know much, but I
但我知道人们去哪里逃避现实
know where people go to get off the grid.
- 这是否意味着你接这个案子了 - 我想把我的钥匙拿回来
- Does this mean you're taking the case? -I want my key back.
离开的我公寓
And get out of my apartment!
还在警队里吗
Still in the force?
你的确是干掉了响尾蛇
Just 'cause you took down Diamondback,
但并不意味着犯罪就消失了
doesn't mean crime went away.
我们是干掉了响尾蛇
We took down Diamondback.
而现在我准备去干掉玛利亚和暗影了
And now I'm ready to take down Mariah and Shades.
我真希望事情可以这么简单
I wish it was that easy.
我知道他们在搞事情
I know their hands are in something.
或许你需要另外一个游离于法律之外的帮手
Maybe you need another assist from outside the law.
- 一个刚从号子里出来的人 - 那是以前的事儿的
- From somebody fresh out of lockup? - That's behind me.
我现在已经把自己的过去弄干净了 我没有什么可隐瞒的了
Now that I've cleared up my past, I've got nothing to hide.
看 我的团队正在处理这件事
Look, my team is on it.
但哈林区会需要你的帮助
But Harlem could use your help...
在你不再和小你的护士缠绵的时候
once you're done spending nights with the nurse
- 是谁把缎带绑在橡树上的（借用黄丝带民谣调侃他） - 你有团队了啊
- who tied the ribbon round the oak tree. - Your team, eh?
在你离开之后 我被任命到一个管辖全市的特遣队
When you left, I got put on a city-wide task force.
听起来是升职了
Sounds like a promotion.
我只能说我的打击的范围可不限于哈林区了
All I can say is my beat isn't just Harlem anymore.
从现在开始 不要再犯错 这里终归还是家
Now, make no mistake, this is still home.
- 无论发生好事还是坏事 - 这里发生了什么
- The good and the bad. - What happened here?
官方说法 一个25岁的男人被发现死在一辆停着的车里
Officially, 25-year-old male found deceased in a parked car.
那非官方的说法呢
And unofficially?
我觉得有些人在利用哈林区的年轻人
I think somebody's been using Harlem's youth
去做那些所谓的深夜任务
for what can only be described as late-night duty.
- 做信使吗 - 可能
- Couriers? - Maybe.
可能还和玛利亚有关
Might even be related to Mariah.
你觉得可能是别的什么吗
You think it's something else.
过去几个月已经有七个类似案例了
Seven in the last few months. Always the same story.
哈林区一个20岁上下的年轻人的把他的母亲从贫民窟搬到了
Harlem 20-something moves his mom out of the projects
新罗谢尔（纽约富人区）一个很好的房子里
into a nice home in New Rochelle.
还是用现金支付的
Down payment in cash.
这些事之间有什么联系吗
What's the connection between them?
你查他们的档案 找人查证 显示
Run their names, you talk to people...
都和枪支毒品无关 仅仅是有了份新的工作 查不到记录
No guns, no drugs, just a new job, off the books.
他们是做什么的 没人知道
Doing what? Nobody knows.
嗯
Hmm.
你做好听真正悲哀的部分了嘛
You ready for the real sad part?
还记得坎迪斯吗 差点就要出庭指控玛利亚了
You remember Candace? This close to testifying against Mariah?
谋杀案还没有破得那个
Murder still unsolved?
她是这个死者的姐姐
That was his sister.
现在这家就剩一个孩子了
Now there's only one.
你应该听听他们母亲的哭声
You should've heard the way their mother cried.
这事你能让我接手多少
How much can you let me in on this?
我会找到幕后主使的
I'll find who's behind it.
你确实可以做到这个
You could do that.
但或者你可以给这个活下来的年轻人指引明路
Or you could help guide this young man in a different direction.
就像老爹曾经做的
The way Pop used to.
你听说过那个清理了克里斯普斯 阿塔克斯的人吗
You hear about that cat that cleaned up Crispus Attucks?
就是他 兄弟
That's him, man.
听说他被关在格鲁吉亚的某个地方
Heard he was locked up somewhere down in Georgia.
保佑我 神父 我身负罪孽
Uh, bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
我已经有 嗯 三天没有忏悔了
It's been... uh, three days since my last confession.
我今天对某人说谎了 一个我爱的人
I lied to someone. Someone I love.
她问我是否想念以前的生活
She asked me if I, uh, miss the life.
我的另外一种生活
The other life that I led.
我告诉她我不想念
And I told her I didn't.
承认谎言的存在
Acknowledging a lie is
往往是通往真理的最好选择 我的孩子
often the best path to finding the truth, son.
这种谎言
A lie like this one...
通常是表明了你自己的犹豫不决
is often a sign of indecision.
表明了你的想法和灵魂并没有统一
A sign that your mind and your soul are not yet aligned.
好吧 我已经非常努力去忽略我的灵魂了
Well, I'm trying very hard to ignore my soul.
主看到的和人看到的不一样
"The Lord sees not as man sees.
人总是看着外在
Man looks on the outward appearance,
但是主 看到的是内心
but the Lord... looks on the heart."
可以详细说说吗 神父
If you could elaborate, Father.
忽略并不能改变任何东西 马修
Ignoring doesn't change anything, Matthew.
上帝知道你的内心
God knows your heart.
让主来帮助你
Let him in so he can help.
- 哪怕那内心已经破损了吗 - 尤其是破损的
- Even if that heart is damaged? - Especially if it's damaged.
马修 我希望和你坦诚地交流
Matthew, I want to talk frankly.
- 请讲 - 你说到的另一个生活
- Please. - This other life you led...
就是你的心之所在吗
is your heart still with it...
还是说你的心更在于那个和你一起经历那个生活的人
or is your heart with the one who walked through it by your side?
是艾丽卡 是的
Elektra. Yeah.
我很想念她
I do miss her.
但是我知道她从我身上发掘出的东西是错的
But I know that the things she brought out of me were wrong.
从你告诉我和她有关的信息中看
From what you've told me about her,
我想她会很高兴你现在过得很好
I think she'd be happy about how well you're doing.
或许吧
Maybe.
或者她会告诉我正抛弃那段生活
Or maybe she'd tell me I'm abandoning that life.
还有对她的记忆
And with it, her memory.
你并没有抛弃艾丽卡 你并不是这样的人
You're not abandoning Elektra. You don't have it in you.
你现在的做法 我们称之为向前看
What you're doing, we call that moving on.
炼狱是为死人准备的 马修 不是活人
Purgatory is a place for the dead, Matthew, not the living.
放下一些人并没有什么问题
There's nothing wrong with letting people go.
她会找到她的安宁的
She'll find her peace.
你希望你也能找到你的安宁
I pray you find yours as well.
你总是很喜欢这个地方
You always liked this spot.
这个公园
It's a miracle...
还存在着 这个城市还没有
the fact that this park even exists.
把这儿拆了建高楼大厦 真是个奇迹
The fact that this city hasn't torn it down to put up high-rises.
对这些人来说 要想象
Must be hard for these people to
整个曼哈顿岛是一片森林的样子肯定很难
imagine the whole island of Manhattan as a forest.
你知道 那些荷兰的殖民者
You know, the Dutch colonists...
当初从原住民手上把曼哈顿买过来的时候
when they bought Manhattan from the natives,
据说才花了24美刀
they're said to have acquired the whole thing for... $24.
要我说 他们买贵了
Ask me, they overpaid.
市长办公室的联系人 他准备好了
The contact at the mayor's office... he's ready.
- 我们多久才能开始 - 三个月
- How soon can we begin? - Three months.
然后我们就进入了最后阶段
Then we move to the final phase.
那就行不通了 现在不行了
That won't work. Not anymore.
- 我们要动作快一点 - 我们之前一致同意
- We need to move faster. - We all agreed.
- 这个方案的 - 此一时彼一时
- This plan, it makes sense. - Made sense.
为了安排这些 我们花了很大的代价
It took great efforts to arrange this.
如果我们加快进度 恐怕会动静太大
If we speed the process, it will not be quiet.
我知道
I'm aware.
我会通知其他人的
I will inform the others.
好 顺便帮我问候一下他们
Good. Send my regards when you do.
然后喂完这些鸟 好吗
And, uh... finish feeding the birds, will you?
它们今天很饿
They're starving today.
你们知道在哪里能找到科尔吗
You guys know where I can find Cole?
和你有什么关系
What's it to you?
往上一楼
Uh, one floor up.
谢谢
Thanks.
我告诉过你们不要再放歌了
Man, I told y'all to stop playing!
我来这里是为了表达我的敬意
I'm here to pay my respects.
凯奇
Cage.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
- 你认识肖恩吗 - 不认识
- Did you know Sean? - No.
但我认识你的姐姐坎迪斯
But I knew your sister Candace.
我想我也是来替她表达敬意的
I guess I'm here to pay my respects for her, too.
这个家庭确实倒霉 不是吗
This family's got some luck, huh?
在这里 不好的事情往往会发生在好人身上
Around here, bad things have a tendency to happen to good people
你觉得你弟弟的死
Do you think your brother's
和她的死有关吗
death could somehow be related to hers?
不 我不觉得
No. I don't think...
不 发生在肖恩身上的事情 更像是一场意外
No, what happened to Sean was, um... was more like an accident.
- 你确定吗 - 是的
- You sure about that? - Yeah.
我听说他找到了一份新工作
I heard he got a new job.
我不知道
I ain't know nothing about that.
我是说 我们并非无话不谈 这是他的事
I mean, we didn't talk about everything. That was his business.
当然
Of course.
你呢
What about you?
什么
What?
情况似乎都还好
Things seem to be going okay.
你有新的工作吗
Did you get a new gig?
没有 我现在正在赋闲状态
No. I'm just in between stuff right now.
你了解吗
I'm always on that hustle, though. You feel me?
我知道
I do.
听着 我可以帮你
Listen... I can help you.
假如 如果你需要什么
Hypothetically speaking, if you ever need anything...
我觉得你应该走了
I think you should go.
问问这个街区的人我做了什么
Ask anybody on this block what I've done.
或者我愿意做什么
Or what I'm willing to do.
你可以相信我
You could trust me.
这些都太晚了
It's too late for all of that.
太晚了 是什么意思
What do you mean, "It's too late"?
- 没什么 - 孩子 没有什么太晚
- Nothing. - Son, it's never too late--
嘿 我不是你的儿子
Yo, man, I ain't your son!
我告诉过你 我什么都不知道
I told you, I don't know a damn thing.
不管你在做什么 你都会伤害你自己的
Whatever you're doing, you're gonna get yourself hurt.
想想你的妈妈
Think about your mom.
她经历了什么
What she's already been through.
我觉得你应该走了
I think you should go.
唯一能帮我的方法是让我也像你一样刀枪不入
The only way to help me is to make me bulletproof, too.
你们这些英雄来得太晚了
It's too late for heroes.
英雄是你说的 我可没这么说
Hero's your word. Not mine.
- 我要我的钱 - 我听到了 我会去拿的
- I want my money. - I hear you. I'm gonna get it.
你今天必须给我钱
You got till the end of the day,
不然我会回来砸烂这地方
or I'm coming back here to bust some shit up!
你好 约翰 雷蒙德 我是杰西卡 琼斯
Hey, John Raymond, it's Jessica Jones.
我是来 回你电话的
I'm, uh... returning your call.
你还记得你打了个电话想吓唬我来着吗
You remember the one where you tried to scare me?
楼下的人说你在这里面
The guy downstairs said you were here.
老兄 我不管你在搞什么
Dude, I don't care what
奇怪的破事 但我们得谈一谈
weird shit you're into, but we gotta talk.
好吧 这门锁得你自己花钱修了
All right, well, you're gonna pay for this.
帮助刺激缓慢发展的欧元区经济
...and help stimulate a slow Eurozone economy...
爆炸物和爆炸物示踪剂(为了观察爆炸物行为和性质而加入的指示剂)
老天
Holy shit.
谢谢
Thank you.
按照你的要求 我们做了安排
We made arrangements, as you requested.
你确定吗
Are you certain about this?
现在还有时间可以考虑清楚的
There's still time to think it through.
你可以走了
You can go.
- 世界上最棒的城市 - 是的
- Greatest city in the world. - Yeah.
纽约人喜欢这么说
New Yorkers like saying that.
不过 在这段时间之后 我
Still, after all this time, I...
我不知道我是怎么想的了
I don't know how I feel about it.
这就是它的美妙之处 它可以是任何你需要的东西
That's the beauty of it. It can be whatever you need it to be.
你需要它成为什么
What do you need it to be?
家
Home.
中央银行周三利率维持不变
...Central Bank on Wednesday kept interest rates unchanged,
顶着加入其他主要重要银行的压力
resisting pressure to join other major central banks...
谢谢
Thanks.
这只是一个城市
It's just a city.
你会习惯看着他们倒下的
You'll get used to watching them fall.
我们得马上下去 爬楼梯
We gotta get down right away. Take the stairs!
快往楼梯下跑
Get down the stairs!
您拨打的电话正忙 请核对后再拨打
...you have dialed. Please check the number and dial again.
m -48.375 2.5 b -44.375 -5.625 -28.5 -8.5 -20.75 -2.875 -23.625 4.625 -39.375 7.75 -48.375 2.5 m -5.25 -56.5 b 5.75 -41.75 -2 -13.75 -14.625 -6.625 -23.875 -14.375 -21.25 -48.125 -5.25 -56.5
m 44.75 -41.75 b 46.25 -41.875 47.5 -42.125 48.875 -42.25 50.125 -42.375 50.625 -41.75 50.75 -40.5 50.75 -38.5 50.375 -38 48.5 -37.875 48.25 -37.875 48 -37.75 47.75 -37.75 46.625 -37.5 45.75 -37.625 45.625 -39.125 45.5 -39.875 45.125 -40.625 44.75 -41.75 m 32.375 -26.375 b 31.375 -30.75 30.375 -35 29.5 -39.25 32.125 -40.875 34.875 -42.375 38.125 -42.25 39.75 -42.25 40.5 -41.75 41 -40.125 42 -37.125 41.75 -34.125 41.5 -31 41.375 -28.875 40.5 -27.75 38.25 -27.5 36.375 -27.375 34.625 -26.75 32.875 -26.375 32.75 -26.375 32.625 -26.375 32.375 -26.375
Orange 字幕组
更多精彩请访问 www.orangesub.com
m -48.375 2.5 b -44.375 -5.625 -28.5 -8.5 -20.75 -2.875 -23.625 4.625 -39.375 7.75 -48.375 2.5 m -5.25 -56.5 b 5.75 -41.75 -2 -13.75 -14.625 -6.625 -23.875 -14.375 -21.25 -48.125 -5.25 -56.5
m 44.75 -41.75 b 46.25 -41.875 47.5 -42.125 48.875 -42.25 50.125 -42.375 50.625 -41.75 50.75 -40.5 50.75 -38.5 50.375 -38 48.5 -37.875 48.25 -37.875 48 -37.75 47.75 -37.75 46.625 -37.5 45.75 -37.625 45.625 -39.125 45.5 -39.875 45.125 -40.625 44.75 -41.75 m 32.375 -26.375 b 31.375 -30.75 30.375 -35 29.5 -39.25 32.125 -40.875 34.875 -42.375 38.125 -42.25 39.75 -42.25 40.5 -41.75 41 -40.125 42 -37.125 41.75 -34.125 41.5 -31 41.375 -28.875 40.5 -27.75 38.25 -27.5 36.375 -27.375 34.625 -26.75 32.875 -26.375 32.75 -26.375 32.625 -26.375 32.375 -26.375
漫威影视联合网飞出品
网飞    原创    剧集
Orange字幕组倾情译制
译：Tam
翻
翻译：  拳本人Bryce君
铁
翻译：地狱厨房的  四伍
七
翻译：qimi g
n
翻译：雨
伞
翻译：  angle
D
校对：手和会大佬  腐君
豆
监制：  发
发
后期：  ilder
W
压制：  啊
洋
邓肯 多特
捍卫者联盟
柬埔寨,金边